# Abi Turner

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A graduate from the Command Shift coding bootcamp seeking a career change into Software Development. A strong enthusiasm and ability to learn new technologies at pace and a desire to utilise and expand skills as a developer. Proven prioritisation and communication skills with over ten years' experience in a retail leadership role.

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Full Stack Developer Student, 10/2022 - 05/2023 Command Shift

- Studied full-stack development using JavaScript and React to create front-end applications integrated to the back-end with API's.
- Worked with Express.js and PostgreSQL for back-end CRUD operations.
- Implemented test-driven development throughout each project using testing frameworks such as Jest and Mocha.
- Learned industry best practices and communicated with tutors and students through stand-ups, retrospectives, and code reviews.
- Collaborated with students on group projects through mob and pair programming.

# Retail Manager, 07/2014 - Current Sainsburys, West Yorkshire

- Accountable as store manager for the performance of both single and dual site stores with an annual turnover of up to £4.3million
- Retail leader accountable for the food operations of stores with an annual turnover of over £15.7million
- Analysing data to identify trends and drive efficiency across locations to deliver key performance measures.
- Exercising strong leadership skills to deliver business change at pace across site teams.
- Effective time management and resource planning between multi-site locations
- Responsible for individual store KPIs and risk management in store.
- Championing diversity and inclusion across the West Yorkshire region including leading the Mentoring Women in Leadership program.

# EDUCATION

Diploma of Higher Education, BTEC Level 3 Animal Management, 2010 - 2012 Park Lane College Leeds Horsforth Centre - Distinction \*

## CONTACT



Halifax, England HX6



07572764861



turner.abi@gmail.com



https://github.com/Abi-Turner

in

https://www.linkedin.com/in/abi-turner94/

# SKILLS

JavaScript

Reac

Node 19

PostgreSQ

Express.

Filenase

Docker

REST APIs

Test Driven Development

Jest

Mocha

React Testing Library

Debuggin

GitHub

Anile Software Methodologie

# **PROJECTS**

## Pizzagram Backenc

Backend service for an Instagram-like application where users can upload and share pictures of pizzas. Built with Node.js, Express, and PostgreSQL, it provides RESTfu APIs for managing user accounts, image uploads, and user interactions such as likes and comments.

#### Pawfect Match

Web application made using React with an integrated API, Firebase Authentication and Firestore for users to create an account, find and save personalised recommendations for dog breeds.

## Surraal Estata

Web application made using React linked to MongoDB where properties can be added, updated, and deleted.

## Weather App

Weather forecasting app built with React that uses live data from an API to display a five-day forecast for a selected location

# Melbourne BBQ Explorer

Map of Melbourne showing all public BBQs Created using EJS, JavaScript, Express, Axios with the Leaflet and Mapbox APIs integrated.

# **INTERESTS**

Guitar & Ukulele || Gaming || Travelling || Reading || Mentoring (mentor working with female leaders in Sainsburys)